i'd welcome back to the table
the style of the two at talk about
data structures in their perot
specially dude
presentation of the above peacekeepers
so you can see pocket heroes you get to
the development version of it
uh... the uh... the first thing go storm
continue that create and you'll pull
typescript
just uh... keybank inayat candy
you statements
carol happens that's really uh... types
of fate
deconstruct rowers those killers parade
contractions
units guitars can contain either
number or a string of conducting a value
all references to one of the complex are
good at the pictures
i want to talk about the uh... that
uh... literal
i each it
data structure heavy balloons back to
speak
fighting it
politicos hijo
richard that first character of the name
of the carnival
sewing killers to help the door signs
interest you have to ask type turning
hashes which is also called the third
experience or look-up tables
uh... are the right person to talk
but we're going to talk about some
speakers
and very bold overexposure to every road
will restore to the door sign
and then
letters and numbers
and underscore so for example you can
have it ready able like this
ordher
if he were brought to you
or you can have a
along the name
and dot com http www kidnappers and
fighter underscore between their divers
or
then you can have it
different
tolong named
uh... this trial do it
full committee
prefers that it can be four mime-version
learning how to learn a lot more
appealing
and uh... underscores between two
variables
not to be told you you can constrict
ideal we've had to be clear or very able
to do you think the mighty versatile
yeah i i think there might very well
to an end
and put in
and that i can print out
i can bring coaxed that variable
thirty-five press now expired
there too
need first of all to see the script
sort of complete script p l
uh... handy too
they open the secretary will be ready to
print out the result full
and just something that uh... windows
but for me
this is the baby for the first at the
clearly the grave of my and then you
find a
to discern ible value and that we can
print it out
you don't have to
assign immediately so he could
it'd be committed variable ten badly
their own assign a value prior on this
i get became result
normally prefer the first version so we
think that the logic of the cold today
unloaded tongue-in-cheek
immediately had become reaction time or
do you find that value
but that does not always possible
severity that they really have to
first declared a variable interest rate
on you could if i can tell you
now what happens to a value
uh... beneath modified if it's not uh...
don't have a value for storage at the
community
it's difficult to tell you the clue
under
undefined it's good to go to mull and
uh...
txt
if you look and all indicative of the
but it's like a different behavior
so for for a couple of the contract with
her death value
that variable has already
some undervalued forty people we have
conducted we can you just heard it
before and can hurt soaked beacon opt
rhetoric defiant and and consultancy
to be fine
dst alice
reused
well you know
and i think i run this code
newsfeed no
and then from
on the other hand if i take it in court
and
excluded copter the excitement as well
done my duty that first it's no
benefited
it could be fined and i think that the
forwarded
value from because this
printing out of the value of after
actually
do printing out of the defined
so you can see the fury it was still not
define here we have to find a value and
he became defied
because later almost had to tell you to
b
under against a little later on for
example he returned to emailed he quotes
to conduct
and done
let me just thought copy-pasting
candidacy in court
at this point it value that we've
already under again
nodded variables
it can contain item numbers or strings
so you can them
that uh... sort of the game you concur
declared variable t
it
and put it in that strength
producing it
and then you can print out a bit of that
variable
and then you can dance trying to do
think that we have all the member
and that you can think of this
particular case
and the five of the cold and you will
see
first before the string and i think not
number
and provoke and care about the problem
types they connect that to abuse
variables
it doesn't air force anything like that
federal
though precursor
government which is you're you
might you might be used there too
the fact that
different day value different variables
be able to type of the variables
prieto rx
behave differently
in peril
that it would be the route than you've
got to trade
what they did a very vocal duet
operas
defied wafted operate or build new
but the operator looking identified how
to operate operant variable speaking
so that started in their example in the
him here and i think i have doorstep
because divorce rate
i can just printed out and and i have
another attorney that will cool day
in here's what it
which is the cost of
and then
also print cult
and almost looks over jerusalem let's
try to
he go instead and ed don't want to leave
and also showed tried to
they don't fit
and those that told you that
and returned to commit boulevard so it's
a look
put to better too
values instilled date
and under-thirty motives that i think
it's a lot of that text
worldwide which is good
would you pick a drawer
or um... repeat and repeat or variable
inappropriate or story
if i run because not all that we get
here
first before you print out the to value
three and four
bend the plots
even edition remember accomplishments of
the completed two values that
to skinner a a very able to values of
them syrianforum epidemic numbers
don't
is the confirmation soon
takes through strength
and the baby please convert it to
numbers into through strength
and print out
done concatenated three and four
before if u
look at this number
and luckily the repetition so we take
the left hand side
content of our staff
picked up a trend
and ben
uh... repeat people
f mangum
times ask you about uh... on the right
hand side
so because of the you have the strength
three
and on the right-hand i_d_ card number
have four times the
corrector st
so if you can see
operate or
you don't want that
cardstock runs how to be here quite a
wrist numbers
or at st
but while capitalistic
what do you
are not really numbers
so what happens if these are
both strengths
if i wrote the code now
will see that the result of the same
because pro automatically convert
numbers to streams
and the strength of numbers when
necessary
spend all free to require c
that's okay um... and what happens if we
won't damage
uh...
change in the middle of the number so
that look at this point what happens in
this case
bronchoscope on the frame
probable care you can
which automatically converts
or coughs
uh... numbers two strings and attempts
to numbers than ever
eat meat
back okay
in the general came
but there are people
they are uh...
this conversion might not be
hundred-percent through
what happens do you think that you he
arranged for example
st point fourteen pt
superseded by the rich
called virtual idaho idea it's called
contact
them believing that uh...
airport is converting the numbers to
because
pro have complex so we have number
numerical compaq
and the string complex
number complex and concoction called
what topic here
so you don't have to worry about fights
pronunciation i did
uh... so what happens in this kid not
have uh... number
and the string that
it looked really comparable to a number
directly
so what happened tonight for a run
discos
that's cool verdicts
the first of three the number three that
uh... printed out the okay
that i got three point fourteen to be
expired
which is just printing company uh... the
content of the world wide
damned attitude warning
and the results ext point fourteen
so this morning is there because we are
trying to jews
uh... yeah
did trained
in a numeric complex
innocent and additional applied in
well exceptional yes in decline
so addictive that limestone very comfy
um...
so the sand
so he can think if you don't
carrom
that the string difficult
got convert it into a number
so we get that morning lobbyist or did
you go back to you only because you
ought to forgive warning lou
it's important to use this morning
otherwise it would be financially doing
something which might be what you want
but that might need to keep some kind of
a problem
so now it's uh...
three point fourteen spy
but and absolute it actually you sort of
a three point fourteen
so what phone bill those invented
picks the left-hand side of the string
and
looks at
looks a bit and tries to use that
definite number
and at that point and it had been state
funeral
stops on the spending it called
converted number
duffel bag orenthal if you disregard of
value
so look for that reason
uh... the the
used produce three point fourteen
uh... the value
all dole are blocking the addition
that what you
much wandered what happened to the whole
wide
desk on purpose
or or reporting it was
albeit addition
so you can stand it
tickled information
that fear
we can to get back to be the three
people formed a door seven to three
point fourteen
it's hyatt
coming from below what i think
unsuitable or why didn't change
bowl wiry
two of the things change
again if you look at the third one
disputed border it
the white items
not you would expect probably back to
the fee
thirteen point fourteen times the that
perpetrating
walked up whole continent print out
according to a leg broke in school
poll numbers so industry
sold
it's built kornberg the three point
fourteen for three and then you've got
forget modification for good
every petition
but you don't see that warming again
at you would normally expect young
what uh...
it because
uh... because the corporation doesn't
get generator warnings so
left click here and then
colon polyps
ankle in two of the cold here
and run it again
and well you'll
heeded the warning in poland
repetition
so earlier if you're just didn't think
it directly into this morning
why didn't he because there was no
warning and the reason we have that at
the time
band edition under admission
very close to the protocols works
the best thing to remember they've
actually supported that number
gameday in a magic
plate indoor garden
so from that point electrical or might
have to value the string value and a
number of endure
at about four to avoid
vehicle version later on
so ben in iraq to this point uh... to
use that repetition operator who didn't
have to convert anymore
so there was no reason to be the warning
brighter
so that uh... how conversions works
and i want to know you all
uh... conclusion virtual numbers to
strengthen from number two string it's
pretty easy injustice fame
their values so you have a number like
three
and if you look at it for three minutes
just to think of the matter st
and it did u street and if you have a
number
extreme gutted about numbers like three
point four q
excuse me if you only had this one
and during this than it wouldn't have a
warning because that's just a number
but because we have uh... something
that's not convenient number
and to get a boarding
so a couple of issued if you'd like to
attend a few more
and a little bit of under
so what happens with undergoing the same
complex
the netscape
that they'd bits of evidence kpr
uh...
mcmichael or white
and uh... because you know thunderstorm
ongoing
to want blue
to printed the lobby haven't declared a
veritable quote
doorstep
uh... and all of our declared loading
didn
give it a value
if well i wrote about
straight comment this article needed
and i promised scored adapted to
warnings
and using the initial too
telling me that i'm trying to get the
mission and values of dismay at the door
blocked love under bolting the admission
ending the coca connection
leaves so you can see that um...
justly boarding fan i'm trying to use
uh...
that resembled a under
i'd working there
number to call back or english does in
context
but the best you can see it's over
though it's a bit difficult to see
say its printing go treatment
and then this
they printing up three a gain
because goal of life opelika on that
in numerical contact it
bc flag zero
adding the scope of the nation idec
three-d_ game
because all doable or wise
bucking the trend contacted bahia flags
and featuring
wanting to make sure that it through
uh... dept dot in that
be fine
and uh...
story that should be steady
not
yeah it shows that i'm old-timer yet
so
i'm running this goes
and that means he's not it's not
declined three handle
uh... probe of using the variable
symbols individual removals and
warik and you can contact
he didn't change a great extent
undefined
so that's what we'll have one thing that
i wanted to show
diverting
you've got some people uh... probably
rightly
and don't like it poll ideal these
warning that they prepare hard-core
exceptions
when something grooms wrong or park show
the world
sold what they can do
if turned aborting into exceptions taken
right here
and anthony and i think old you to join
every morning
into uh... fatal exception
so if i go to you know i mean by that
studied stupid
display
and rhonda code
so i get
dreams
the first picked up
the first thing here
and then that i'm trying to add to that
used to print
if we print out the warning well that
warning did not feel an exception
so descriptors of dread
who were killed
so that's one of the other thing if you
want to be you'd be the extreme and
getting exception to the state
but what if you want to look at what we
can hold thing at all so what if you
want to make sure that the great value
growth
probably from canberra from the outside
world
attitudes
actually retarded
looks like a number of before you
actually can
kornberg
support that he would use and module
attaced color
usual and that's what role
transplant function
looks like number
and then you can do that function stands
before you actually called me
uh... park that moved
and number two no so you would see
looks like number
blore that
and
looks like number
toward life
and only then i would think that would
do
pitchfork
so dad additional do only if peeps are
boom so the numbers
and that i can run this code
and there isn't that correct
c_v_r_
line sixteen
it tells me i forgot
close destructive
that's right again
well you can see that they have the
number three and that i have the result
of the kolkata mission and the define
cute
but i don't have an exception
and if i'd have
value like this
value which is really
looks like a member and ironic
then in addition to the cope with the
nation your are also have the admission
so that it
uh... about skimmers and a teacher
actually wondering if there is still
pretty fooling control so they were
guilty
but with an advanced topics that we are
not going to address it now
and uh... i think that's a lot of kits
reform went through next time